<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--
        !! IMPORTANT!!
        Any significant updates to the contents this file need to update
        the following revision number to notify users!
    -->
    <integer name="usage_revision">2</integer>

    <string name="usage_title">"Usage and Privacy Agreement"</string>
    <string name="usage_decline_action">Decline</string>
    <string name="usage_agree_action">I Understand and Agree</string>

    <string name="usage_legal_services_title">Legally Restricted Services</string>
    <string name="usage_legal_services_section1">
        This software provides access and tools for the amateur radio APRS
        network. Radio communications are a regulated service.
    </string>
    <string name="usage_legal_services_section2">
        Some of the functionality provided by this application can be used
        in ways that may require a license or be restricted in your area.
        It is your responsibility to research and follow local laws when using
        this software.
    </string>

    <string name="usage_data_privacy_title">Data Privacy</string>
    <string name="usage_data_privacy_section1">
        This application can be used to transmit your location and other
        information to the APRS radio network. When transmitted, the
        information you provide, including but not limited to your location,
        will be transmitted publicly, either by radio or by an internet service,
        and should not be considered private.
    </string>
    <string name="usage_data_privacy_section2">
        This application collects usage data using Google Firebase.
        Information collected may include information unique to your device,
        information about actions performed within the application,
        and logging data related to using the application.
        This information is used internally to improve the application
        and is not shared with any 3rd parties.
    </string>

    <string name="usage_warranty_title">No Warranty</string>
    <string name="usage_warranty_section1">
        THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
        EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF
        MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.
        IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY
        CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT,
        TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH
        THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
    </string>

    <string name="usage_rights_title">Software Rights</string>
    <string name="usage_rights_section1">
        Copyright (c) 2020-2022 Ink Applications
    </string>
    <string name="usage_rights_section2">
        This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.
    </string>
    <string name="usage_rights_section3">
        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.
    </string>
    <string name="usage_rights_section4">
        The full license can be obtained at:
        http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/gpl-2.0.html
        The full license, as well as sources can be obtained at:
        https://ack.inkapplications.com
        or by emailing: legal@inkapplications.com
    </string>
</resources>
